thisisrnb.com 2019-08-30

# PRIVACY | ThisisRnB.com - New R&B Music, Artists, Playlists, Lyrics

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at ThisisRnB.com (“company”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about our policy, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at info@thisisrnb.com.

This privacy policy applies to all information collected through our website, and/or any related services, sales, marketing or events.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

When you visit this website, we may collect certain information from and about you. This includes things like your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, and the last domain you visited before coming to our website or the domain you go to when you leave. It also includes various statistical data such as which pages you visit on the website, how long you stay on them, and what you click.

We may place a “cookie” on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes a unique identifier, sent to your browser from a website’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We may use cookies to keep track of your choice of language and home page preference; to understand your exposure to certain Internet advertisements as you use the website, and to gather usage data that will help us generally improve the quality of the website. There is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept cookies. You should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you with certain features on the website. We also may use a small piece of code (sometimes referred to as “1×1 clear pixel,” “Web beacon” or “clear GIF”) placed in the pages of the website to help us gather additional information about which parts of the site receive the most visitors and other user traffic patterns, and enable us to administer the site.

Furthermore, we collect information from and about you when you specifically provide it to us. For example, in connection with your use of certain features, offers, or contests through the website you may be asked to provide certain information including your name, email addresses, address, and telephone number.

**WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?**

We only share information with your consent, to comply with laws, to protect your rights, or to fulfill business obligations.

We only share and disclose your information in the following situations:

• Compliance with Laws. We may disclose your information where we are legally required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, governmental requests, a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena (including in response to public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements).

• Vital Interests and Legal Rights. We may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding potential violations of our policies, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person and illegal activities, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.

• Vendors, Consultants and Other Third-Party Service Providers. We may share your data with third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform services for us or on our behalf and require access to such information to do that work. Examples include: payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service and marketing efforts. We may allow selected third parties to use tracking technology on the Sites, which will enable them to collect data about how you interact with the Sites over time. This information may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. Unless described in this Policy, we do not share, sell, rent or trade any of your information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

**DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?**

We do not knowingly collect data from or market to children under 13 years of age.

We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 13 years of age. By using the website, you represent that you are at least 13 or that you are the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent to such minor dependent’s use of the website. If we learn that personal information from users less than 13 years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 13, please contact us at info@thisisrnb.com.

**WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?**

In some regions, such as the European Economic Area, you have rights that allow you greater access to and control over your personal information. You may review, change, or terminate your account at any time.

In some regions (like the European Economic Area), you have certain rights under applicable data protection laws. These may include the right (i) to request access and obtain a copy of your personal information, (ii) to request rectification or erasure; (iii) to restrict the processing of your personal information; and (iv) if applicable, to data portability. In certain circumstances, you may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information. To make such a request, please use the contact details provided below. We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

If we are relying on your consent to process your personal information, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note however that this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before its withdrawal.

Cookies and similar technologies: Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our website. 

**CONTACT US**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

info@thisisrnb.com
